const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
  {
    question: 'ὀκτώ',
    answers: ['acht'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἐννέα',
    answers: ['negen'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἕνδεκα',
    answers: ['elf'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δεκατρεῖς',
    answers: ['dertien'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δεκατέσσαρες',
    answers: ['veertien'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δεκαπέντε',
    answers: ['vijftien'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δεκαέξ',
    answers: ['zestien'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δεκαεπτά',
    answers: ['zeventien'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δεκαοκτώ',
    answers: ['achttien'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δεκαεννέα',
    answers: ['negentien'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'εἴκοσι',
    answers: ['twintig'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'τριάκοντα',
    answers: ['dertig'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'πεντήκοντα',
    answers: ['vijftig'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἑξήκοντα',
    answers: ['zestig'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἑβδομήκοντα',
    answers: ['zeventig'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ὀγδοήκοντα',
    answers: ['tachtig'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἐνενήκοντα',
    answers: ['negentig'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'διακόσιοι',
    answers: ['tweehonderd'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'τριακόσιοι',
    answers: ['driehonderd'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'τετρακόσιοι',
    answers: ['vierhonderd'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'χίλιοι',
    answers: ['duizend'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'χίλιαι',
    answers: ['duizend'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'χίλια',
    answers: ['duizend'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'πρῶτος',
    answers: ['eerste'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δεύτερος',
    answers: ['tweede'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'τρίτος',
    answers: ['derde'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'τέταρτος',
    answers: ['vierde'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'πέμπτος',
    answers: ['vijfde'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἕκτος',
    answers: ['zesde'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἕβδομος',
    answers: ['zevende'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ὄγδοος',
    answers: ['achtste'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἔνατος',
    answers: ['negende'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δέκατος',
    answers: ['tiende'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'πεντηκοστός',
    answers: ['vijftigste'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἅπαξ',
    answers: ['eenmaal'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δίς',
    answers: ['tweemaal'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'τρίς',
    answers: ['driemaal'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'τετράκις',
    answers: ['viermaal'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'πεντάκις',
    answers: ['vijfmaal'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἑξάκις',
    answers: ['zesmaal'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἑπτάκις',
    answers: ['zevenmaal'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ὀκτάκις',
    answers: ['achtmaal'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'ἐνάκις',
    answers: ['negenmaal'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'δεκάκις',
    answers: ['tienmaal'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  }
]
const lesson32Numbers: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson32-numbers',
  name: 'Les 32 – Overige getallen',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson32Numbers
